# **HANS OLIVEIRA**

+1 (647) 879 3948 | hansnery@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/hansnery/ | Toronto, ON GitHub: https://github.com/hansnery | Portfolio: https://hansnery.github.io/portfolio/

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full-stack Developer with nearly 4 years of coding experience, a team-oriented approach, and a passion for software, web, and game development. Eager to apply and expand my technical skills in an internship or Junior Full-stack Developer role. Exceptional problem-solving abilities and excellent communication skills.

# **SKILLS HIGHLIGHTS**

Ruby On Rails	SQL, PostgreSQL, and MongoDB	Self-starter
Python	NodeJS, Express JS, and React	Self-learner
Javascript	Bootstrap, Bulma and Tailwind	Communicative
Java	Modding and Game Development	Team Player
PHP	Adobe Photoshop	Persistent
1111	Adobe i flotosilop	i Ci sisterit

## **EDUCATION**

**Diploma / Computer Programming**, Georgian@ILAC, Toronto, ON. Sep 2022 – Apr 2024

**BA in International Relations**, Unisul, Florianópolis, Brazil. Aug 2012 – Dec 2015

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Coding Instructor Jan 2024 – Present

**Kids Coding** 

Toronto

- Develop and deliver engaging coding curriculum tailored for children and teenagers.
- Utilize various programming languages and tools suitable for beginners, such as HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Assess and track student progress, providing personalized feedback and support.
- Stay updated with the latest trends in technology and education to incorporate into the curriculum.

Georgian@ILAC

Toronto

- Offer individualized support to students on programming projects through one-on-one sessions and peer programming, aiding in troubleshooting, concept comprehension, skill enhancement, and portfolio development.
- Develop and lead workshops, delivering presentations to students to foster essential skills such as proficiency in version control software, frameworks, and algorithms.
- Spearheaded the launch of Georgian@ILAC's inaugural Computer Programming Lab, independently developing foundational processes to enhance student skill sets and facilitate portfolio building.

## Parliamentary Assistant - Digital Strategist

Feb 2020 – Sep 2022

Legislative Assembly of the State of Santa Catarina Florianópolis, Brazil

- Created and designed digital content, including graphics and videos, to enhance the Congressman's online presence and increase engagement with constituents.
- Handled the Congressman's social media profiles, informing the public of public policies, important bills and promoting key initiatives.
- Contributed to the Congressman's re-election campaign, witnessing an increase in votes from 38,547 to 71,185 during my tenure.

## **MAIN PROJECTS**

#### **Denison Roof Experts Website**

- **Technologies used:** PHP for the Backend and Tailwind CSS for the Frontend.
- **Description:** Created a website for a roofing company based in Toronto.
- **Outcome:** Modernized the client's outdated web presence, resulting in improved user experience and increased engagement metrics.
- Link: Denison Roof Experts

#### The Bugger

- Technologies used: Ruby On Rails, Bulma, and PostgreSQL. Deployed on Heroku.
- **Description:** A mock social media platform for developers inspired on Facebook.
- Outcome: Implemented features such as authentication, timeline, friending, liking and commenting.
- Link: The Bugger

## Age of the Ring: Realms in Exile

- **Technologies used:** LUA, Blender, and Adobe Photoshop.
- Description: A mod for Electronic Art's strategy game The Lord of the Rings: Battle for Middle-Earth II.
- Outcome: Has over 3200 downloads and around 270 people on the mod's Discord server.
- Link: Age of the Ring: Realms in Exile ModDB Page